Guide to the Documenting the COVID-19 experience at MSU Collection
Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Documenting the COVID-19 experience at MSU
2020
Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections P.O. Box 173320, Centennial Mall Montana State University
Collection 2661
20 folders Born digital
Montana State University Library's Archives and Special Collections documentation of the COVID-19 pandemic's affect on the MSU campus.
The materials in this collection represent the range of the MSU community's response to the pandemic, from the very personal to the administrative. The bulk of the collection consists of student responses to COVID-19 related assignments in courses across disciplines beginning in Spring 2020. Together these records constitute an archive of lived experiences during this time.
The COVID-19 pandemic universally upended daily life beginning in March 2020 in both expected and unexpected ways. Members of the Montana State University (MSU) community reacted and adapted as needed in our personal, professional, and scholastic lives. MSU Library's Archives and Special Collections documented this new reality by soliciting written reflections and other records of life during the 2020 pandemic from MSU students, staff, and faculty.
Collection is open for research. The identities of some authors have been redacted at their request.
College and Universities; Bozeman; Medicine and Health; Mental Health; Montana
- Spring 2020, 1
  - CLS 101 COVID-19 Assignment
  - ANTY 242 Contemporary Japan COVID-19 Assignment
  - ANTY 428 COVID-19 Assignment
  - NCUR Reflection EDSP 307
  - NCUR Reflection EDSP 306
  - RLST203D Spring 2020 COVID Responses
  - RLST321 Spring 2020 Final Discussion
  - EDEC 385 COVID-19 Time Capsule
  - ARTZ 217 COVID-19 Assignment
  - GPHY 365 Geographical Planning COVID-19
  - EDSP 458 NCUR Reflection
  - EQUH 110 Western Equitation COVID-19 Response
  - EQUH 207 Intermediate English Equitation COVID-19 Assignment
  - Myth and Belief COVID-19 Responses
  - Gender in America - COVID-19 Journal Assignment
  - HSTR 416 COVID Food Journal Assignment
  - WRIT 201 COVID extra credit - Massey
  - WRIT 326 COVID assignment
  - RLST206IH (ORIGINS OF GOD) COVID Responses
- Summer 2020, 2
  - Honors Academy Summer 2020 Taking the Pulse of Montana